MacKaye Family papers ML-5
Rauner Special Collections Library
- William Payson MacKaye, 1874-1906; 14
  - Box: 28, 1874-1906 (Box 28)
    - Sketchbook: "My Second Child", 1883 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Sketchbook: "Just The Thing", 1882 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Sketches, Artwork, Clippings, undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Paintings and Sketches, 1880's (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Paintings and Sketches, 1874-1887 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Art Education Textbooks, 1875 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Sketchbook, 1883-1884 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Notebook, 1885 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Sketchbooks, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Notebook, 1881 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Sketchbook, 1888 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Sketchbook, undated (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Sketchbook, 1885 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Sketchbook, 1868 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Box: 29, 1871-1955 (Box 29)
    Box: 29
    - Sketchbook, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Notebooks and Blank Notepads of the "MacKaye School of Acting", undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Sketchbooks, 1887 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Sketchbook, 1871 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Sketchbooks, 1887 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: William Payson MacKaye from Frank B. Steele, 1888 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: William Payson MacKaye from May Monroe, 1877-1888 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: William Payson MacKaye Miscellaneous, 1883-1889 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: William Payson MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1879-1888 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: William Payson MacKaye to Sarah Stetson Pevear, 1879-1888 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: William Payson MacKaye to Steele MacKaye, 1879-1886 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: William Payson MacKaye Miscellaneous and Other Members of Family, 1887-1888 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Typed Copies of Above Mentioned Correspondence, 1879-1888 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Biographical Sketches, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Loose Correspondence, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Church Bulletins "All Soul's Monthly ", 1888-1890 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Biographical Material, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Writings, 1880's (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Reminiscences, 1883-1905 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- James Medbery MacKaye, 1871-1955; 15
  Contains correspondence, writings, notes, clippings, programs, pamphlets and ephemera
  - Box: 29, 1871-1955 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Benton MacKaye, 1907-1933 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1887-1891 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1892-1918 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Mary Morse MacKaye, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Percy MacKaye, 1908-1930 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Sarah Stetson Pevear, 1888-1901 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Steele MacKaye, 1881-1894 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Box: 30, 1883-1968 (Box 30)
    Box: 30
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye to Other members of the Family, 1895-1921 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye from W.G. Bannister, 1906-1907 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye from Mary Morse MacKaye (Peggy), Newspaper Clippings, 1906-1968 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye Regarding Bird Banding, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye Miscellaneous, 1883-1895 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye Miscellaneous, 1896-1898 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye Miscellaneous, 1896-1898 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: James Medbery MacKaye Miscellaneous, 1899-1906 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Notes: Philosophy, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Notes: Philosophy, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Notes: Philosophy, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Programs, Reviews, Wedding Announcements and Invitations, Photographs and Ephemera, 1880's-1932 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Bulletins, Programs, Writings, 1890's-1914 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Published Book "The Happiness Of Nations" by James Medbery MacKaye, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Writing: MS "The Logic Of Language", undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Box: 31, 1893-1945 (Box 31)
    Box: 31
    - Notes: "The Logic Of Language", undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Notes: "The Logic Of Language", undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Writing: The Logic Of Language" Rough Draft, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Notes: "The Logic Of Language", undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Writing: Typescript "The Logic Of Language", 1929 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Magazine and Newspaper Articles by James Medbery MacKaye, 1903-1932 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets by James Medbery MacKaye, 1915-1920 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Writing: Poems, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Articles on "Bird Banding", 1922-1924 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Magazine and Newspaper Articles, 1900-1930 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Obituaries for James Medbery MacKaye, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Percy MacKaye, 1870-1945, 1954, 1975; 16
  Contains correspondence, financial receipts and bills, business correspondence, finished and unfinished manuscripts of plays, masques, pageants and poems, drafts and other writings related to "Epoch" and "Annals Of An Era", programs, pamphlets, clippings, reviews and articles, photographs, theatrical stills and scrapbooks
  - Box: 31, 1893-1945 (Box 31)
    - Biographical material: Harvard College, 1893-1897 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Birthday Celebrations, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Percy MacKaye Memorial Committee, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Bank Statements, 1927-1930 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Financial Receipts A, 1888-1919 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Financial Receipts B, 1908-1927 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Financial Receipts C, 1907-1919 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Box: 32, 1898-1929 (Box 32)
    Box: 32
    - Financial Receipts D-G, 1908-1929 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Financial Receipts H-K, 1908-1927 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Financial Receipts L, 1908-1927 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Financial Receipts M, 1908-1924 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Financial Receipts N, 1908-1928 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Financial Receipts O-Q, 1908-1923 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Financial Receipts R, 1907-1914 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Financial Receipts S, 1907-1929 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Financial Receipts T-V, 1908-1928 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Financial Receipts W-Z, 1909-1929 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Financial Receipts Miscellaneous, 1903-1914 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Unreceipted Bills A-J, 1915-1917 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Unreceipted Bills K-Z, 1916-1928 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Business Letters, 1898 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Business Letters, 1902 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Business Letters, 1903 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Business Letters, 1904 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Business Letters, 1905 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Business Letters, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Business Letters, 1907 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Business Letters A-B, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Business Letters C-D, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Business Letters E-G, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Business Letters H-L, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Business Letters M-R, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Business Letters S-Z, 1908 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Business Letters A, 1909 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Business Letters B, 1909 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Business Letters C, 1909 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Box: 33, 1909-1919 (Box 33)
    Box: 33
    - Business Letters D, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Business Letters E, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Business Letters F, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Business Letters G, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Business Letters H, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Business Letters I, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Business Letters J, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Business Letters K, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Business Letters L, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Business Letters M, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Business Letters N, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Business Letters O, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Business Letters P, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Business Letters Q-R, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Business Letters S, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Business Letters T, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Business Letters U-Z, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Business Letters A-B, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Business Letters C-D, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Business Letters E-H, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Business Letters I-L, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Business Letters M-O, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Business Letters P-R, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Business Letters S-T, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Business Letters U-Z, 1910 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Business Letters A-B, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Business Letters C-D, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Business Letters E-H, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Business Letters I-L, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Business Letters M-O, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Business Letters P-R, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Business Letters S-T, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Business Letters U-Z, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Business Letters A-B, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Business Letters C, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Business Letters F, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Business Letters I, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Business Letters K, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Business Letters L, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Business Letters M-N, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Business Letters P-R, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Business Letters S, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Business Letters W, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Business Letters A-B, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Business Letters C-D, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Business Letters E-G, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Business Letters H-J, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Business Letters K-M, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Business Letters N-R, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Business Letters S And Other Pertaining to St. Louis Pageant, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Business Letters T-Z and undated, 1914 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Business Letters, 1915-1917 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Business Letters A-B, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Business Letters C-D, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Box: 34, 1886-1945 (Box 34)
    Box: 34
    - Business Letters E-H, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Business Letters I-K, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Business Letters L-M, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Business Letters N-R, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Business Letters S-Z, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Business Letters A-B, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Business Letters C-D, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Business Letters E-H, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Business Letters I-K, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Business Letters L-M, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Business Letters N-R, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Business Letters S-Z, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Business Letters, 1921-1926 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Business Letters, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Business Letters A-L, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Business Letters M-Z, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Business Letters, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Business Letters, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Business Letters, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Arvia MacKaye, 1906-1908 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Benton MacKaye, 1896-1945 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Harold Steele MacKaye, 1893 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Hazel MacKaye, 1889-1928 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to James Medbery MacKaye, 1897-1928 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1886-1891 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1892-1894 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1895-1899 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye, 1900-1917 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Mary Medbery MacKaye from Europe, 1899-1901 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Box: 35, 1880-1956 (Box 35)
    Box: 35
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Robert Keith MacKaye, 1903-1930 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Sarah Stetson Pevear, 1893-1900 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Steele MacKaye, 1883-1890 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to William Payson MacKaye, 1887-1888 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye with Other Relatives, 1909-1928 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1880-1914 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1880-1914 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1915-1956 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Autograph Requests and Requests from Students Seeking Information, 1908-1930 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1909-1931 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Undated and/or Unidentified (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Envelopes, 1920-1927 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1906 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye February-April, 1906 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye May-November, 1906 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye January-June, 1907 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye September-December, 1907 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Box: 36, 1908-1911 (Box 36)
    Box: 36
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye January, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye April, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye May-July, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye August, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye September, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye October-November, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye January-February, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye March-April, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye May-July, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye September-December, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye January-February, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye March, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye April-June, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye August-December, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye January, 1911 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye February, 1911 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Box: 37, 1898-1927 (Box 37)
    Box: 37
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye March-April, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye June-July, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye October-November, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1912 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye to Marion Morse MacKaye, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1898 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1903 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1904 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1905 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1905 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye January-June, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye January-June, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye July-December, 1906 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye January-June, 1907 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye July-December, 1907 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye January-June, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye July, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye August, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye October-November, 1908 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye February-April, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye May-July, September-December, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Box: 38, 1870-1929 (Box 38)
    Box: 38
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye January-March, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye April-May, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, August-September, November-December 1910 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye January-March, 1911 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye April-July, October, 1911 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye January-June, 1912 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Percy MacKaye from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1917-1920, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Non Family A-Ale; Abbot, John Moseley; Abbot; Ernest H.; Abbot, Lyman; Abel, L.Hosford; Adams, Herbert; Adams, Maude; Adams, Oscar Fay; Adams, Samuel Hopkins; Addams, Jane; Adler, Felix; Adler, Laurence; Alden, H.M.; Alexander, Hartley Barr; Alexander, James W.II; Alexander, John White and Elizabeth A, 1897-1924 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence Non Family All-Ans; Allen, James Lane; Allen, Viola; Alling, Elisie Dwight; Alling, Kenneth; Alling, Millicent B., Allinson, Francis G.; Ames, Winthrop; Angell, Norman; Anglin, Margaret; Anspacher, Louise Kaufman, 1907-1925 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence Non Family Arc-Aus; Archer, Rosalie; Archer, William; Ardison, G.; Arnold, A.G.; Atherton, Gertrude; Atherton, Lucius; Auerbach, Joseph S.; Austin, Mary, 1908-1928 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence Non Family Ba; Bacheller, Irving A.; Bainton, George; Baker, Bertha Kunz; Baker, Edward O.; Baker, George Pierce; Baker, Ray Stannard; Baldwin, Charles C.; Ballinger, R.A.; Bangs, John Kendrick; Barker, Granville, 1907-1928 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence Non Family Ba; Barnard, George Grey; Barrett, Robert and Katharine; Barron, Ellwyn; Barrows, Samuel J.; Barry, Beatrice; Baynes, Ernest Harold; Baynes, Louise, 1900-1928 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence Non Family Be-Bi; Beach, Rex E.; Beede, A.McG.; Beeler, Family; Beesley, Lawrence; Belasco, David; Belmont, Eleanor Robson; Bender, Elizabeth Dewin; Beneker, Gerrit A.; Bennet, James O'Donnell; Betts, Craven Langstroth; Biddle, Ellen McG.; Bigelow, Poultney; Binyon, Laurence; Bispham, David Scull, 1912-1925 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence Non Family Bl-Bo; Blair, John; Blashfield, Edwin Howland; Bok, Edward William; Bolton, C.K.; Boni, Charles; Booth, Leonora; Borglum, Gutson; Botkin, Ben A.;Bowen, Henry; Bowker Company, 1909-1928 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence Non Family Br; Bradford, Gamaliel; Bradley, Florence; Bragdon, Claude; Brahan, Lionel; Braithwaite, William S.; Branch, Anne Hempstead; Brett, George R.; Bridges, Robert; Brinton, Christian; Brooks, John Graham; Brown, Alfred H.; Brown, Alice; Brown, Frank Chouteau; Brown, Maurice; Browne, Waldo R.; Brunner, Arnold W.; Brush, George de Forest; Bryce, Lord, 1909-1929 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence Non Family Bu-By; Buchanan, Helen; Burbank, Luther; Buchard, Lewis S.; Burgess, Gelett; Burnett, Vivian; Burns, E.F.; Burritt, William Nelson; Burton, Richard; Butler, Henry A.; Butler, Nicholas Murray; Bynner, Witter, 1909-1929 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence Non Family Ca-Cl; Cady, Daniel L.; Calder, Chester T.; Campbell, M.; Cmpbell, Stella; Carlyle, Grace; Carman, Bliss; Carpenter, Anna M.; Carrell, Alexis; Cart, Doris; Carter, Herbert; Carter, Huntley; Cate, Curtis Wesley; Cather, Willa S.; Cawein, Madison; Chadwick, George W.; Champollion, Andre; Channing, Edward; Chase, Jennie F.; Cheatham, Kitty; Cheever, David; Cheney, Sheldon; Choate, Joseph; Chubb, Percival; Chubb, R.W.; Church Company; Churchill, Winston; Clapp, Henry Austin; Clark, Lotta; Clarke, Francis S.; Clarke, Helen Archibald; Clemens, Samuel Langhorn; Cleveland, Grover; Clevelend, Mary B.; Clifton, Chalmers, 1870-1914 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence Non Family Co; Coates, Walter J.; Cobb, Irwin S.; Coburn, Charles D.; Coburn, Ivah Willis; Collier, Constance; Colton, Anne; Colum, Padraic; Colvin, Mary E.; Conklin, Grace H.; Converse, Frederick S.; Cook, Howard W.; Copeau, Jacques; Copeland, C.T.; Corbin, John; Cort, Sam; Corte, Louis; Cox, B.F.; Cox, Kenyon, 1918-1929 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence Non Family Cr-Cu; Craig, Edward Gordon; Crockett, Walter H.; Croly, Herbert; Crosman, Henrietta; Crothers, Samuel; Crow, Martha Foote, Curry, S.S., 1909-1928 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Box: 39, 1903-1930 (Box 39)
    Box: 39
    - Correspondence Non Family Da; Daly, Arnold; Damrosch, Walter and Margaret B.; Dargan, Olive; Dartmouth College; Davenport, Charles B.; Davenport, Howard; Davidge, Clara Sidney; Davidson, C.A.; Davis, Emily C.; Davis, Fannie Stearns; Davis, James J.; Davis, John W.; Davison, Wilfred; Dawley, Herbert M., 1909-1929 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Non Family De-Di; Dean, Joseph; De Koven, Reginald; Deming, Alden O.; Deming, Kathryn; Densmore, John H.; Depew, Chauncey M.; Derby, Roger Alden; Dewey, John; Dewing, Maria Oakey; Dickinson, Thomas H.; Dithmar, Edward; Dixey, Henry E., 1913-1929 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence Non Family Do-Dv; Dobson, Helen A.C.; Dodd, Lee; Dodge, Mabel; Doggett, Frank A.; Dole, Nathan H.; Doubleday, Doran and Company; Dowling, Adele Neill; Dransfield, Jane; Drewson, G.; Dreyfus, Lilian S.; Drinkwater, John; Duffield; Duncan, Anne H.; Duncan, Augustin; Duncan, Isadora; Dunn; Sara; Duryea, Viola; Dvorak, Georgia, 1912-1929 (Box 39, Folder 3)